<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Featured on Jupiter Broadcasting</title><link>https://jb.codefighters.net/categories/featured/</link><description>Recent content in Featured on Jupiter Broadcasting</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 04:10:01 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jb.codefighters.net/categories/featured/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Linux Action News</title><link>https://jb.codefighters.net/show/linux-action-news/240-linux-action-news/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 04:10:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://jb.codefighters.net/show/linux-action-news/240-linux-action-news/</guid><description>Episode Links Why is the open source driver release from NVidia so important for Linux? | Christian F.K. Schaller — Today NVidia announced that they are releasing an open source kernel driver for their GPUs, so I want to share with you some background information and how this will impact Linux graphics and compute going forward. NVIDIA Releases Open-Source GPU Kernel Modules — This release is a significant step toward improving the experience of using NVIDIA GPUs in Linux, for tighter integration with the OS and for developers to debug, integrate, and contribute back.</description></item><item><title>Mike's Magic Mom</title><link>https://jb.codefighters.net/show/coderradio/465-mikes-magic-mom/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 04:10:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://jb.codefighters.net/show/coderradio/465-mikes-magic-mom/</guid><description>After solving a moral dilemma in our particular kind of way, Mike dishes on some ambitious plans that might kick off a new era of development for him.
Episode Links</description></item><item><title>Automated Chaos</title><link>https://jb.codefighters.net/show/linuxun/457-automated-chaos/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 04:10:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://jb.codefighters.net/show/linuxun/457-automated-chaos/</guid><description>Episode Links New NASA Black Hole Sonifications with a Remix — In some ways, this sonification is unlike any other done before because it revisits the actual sound waves discovered in data from NASA&amp;rsquo;s Chandra X-ray Observatory. The popular misconception that there is no sound in space originates with the fact that most of space is essentially a vacuum, providing no medium for sound waves to propagate through. A galaxy cluster, on the other hand, has copious amounts of gas that envelop the hundreds or even thousands of galaxies within it, providing a medium for the sound waves to travel.</description></item><item><title>Our Cuban Car Moment</title><link>https://jb.codefighters.net/show/coderradio/464-our-cuban-car-moment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 04:10:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://jb.codefighters.net/show/coderradio/464-our-cuban-car-moment/</guid><description>Episode Links Episode 5: End of the Petrodollar - Weirdly, not alarmist Episode 14: Can&amp;rsquo;t spell stagflation without oil and gas Leaf Node Monitoring - Leaf Node — Open Source (GPLv3) Network Monitoring for Windows, Linux &amp;amp; Android. Written in C++ &amp;amp; Qt 5. Perfect to run on your desktop and monitor your servers. Simple setup, auto-detects running services, runs checks concurrently, open port scanning and alerting. Hosts with failed checks automatically rise to the top, everything that’s okay stays nice and green.</description></item></channel></rss>